找我的人
My man.
不该只有290块
Ain't but $290 here.
该死 Frog
Goddamn it, frog,
一般G-Pack的批发价是400到500
让你销值1000的货 回扣该是500
When you work a g-Pack for a guy... a kickback's supposed to be $500.
藏毒点被端了
Stash got hit, yo.
我不要听这些! 我只要我的钱!
I ain't hearing that shit! I want my fucking money!
你最好搞清楚我不是玩过家家 混球
You'd best know i ain't playing, motherfucker.
好吧 你想玩是吧
Okay, that's how you want it?
可以 但我明天再来时
Fine! But when i roll back past here tomorrow,
钱最好够数
Money gonna be right,
否则走着瞧吧
Or you gonna see.
看看你得罪的是谁
You gonna see who you're fucking with!
难道我看着像废物不成
Do i look like a fucking punk?
嘿 小鬼 给我到街角 买瓶Snapple(果味饮料)和一包蟹肉条
Yo, shorty. Get me a snapple and a bag of crab chips from the corner.
你他妈搞什么 白痴?
What the fuck is your problem, asshole?
靠 怎么遇上这破事
Fuck, this is bad shit!
靠 糟透了
Fuck, this is really bad.
该死
Shit.
滚下车
Get your ass out that car.
就下
All right!
闭嘴
Shut up.
钱在哪
Where the money at?
查查袜子
Check his socks.
你有什么要给我吗 Zig?
You got something for me here, zig?
有些钱要给我吗 伙计?
You got some dough for me, man?
上帝 有了!
Jesus, jackpot.
老天
Jesus.
等会 伙计 就这么点可算不上钱啊
Man, hold up, man. Ain't enough here to really call this shit money, man.
Cheese 别冲动 我正在想办法
Cheese, take it easy, i'm working on it.
但你知道 我的人...
But my people, you know....
你它妈的当这是干什么 伙计?
What the fuck you think this is, man?
怎么 你觉得还能换个花样玩?
What, you think this supposed to get played some other way?
你是这么想的吗 伙计?
Is that what you think, man?
该死 狗娘养的 很痛啊
Damn it, son of a bitch, that hurt.
是啊 我也知道
Yeah, i know it did.
好吧 你看这件大衣怎么样
All right, look, how about the coat?
大衣给你 行了吧
Take the coat, all right?
我为它花了两千大洋呢
I paid two large for it...
那么 再加上我给你的现钞...
So that, plus the cash i gave you...
周末我就再给你700块
And then i can get $700 more by the end of the week.
你知道我会照付的
You know i will!
那里能缝好的
You know right there, you can fix that.
2000块?
$2,000?
就这玩意儿?
For this?
就算穿在咱黑人身上也显不出范
Not even a black man could style that shit.
懂我的意思吗 伙计们?
You know what i'm saying, man?
你笑什么笑啊?
What you laughing at, man?
冷静 不要激动
Chill, be cool about it.
我周五把钱给你
I'll get your money by friday.
到时你就知道 根本不用这么大动干戈
Then you'll see there's no need to get all fucking dramatic out here!
听着 伙计 如果我周五拿不到钱
Look, man, if i ain't paid by friday,
周六就是你的死期
You dead by saturday, man.
嘿 把他的破车收了
Yo, take my man's ride.
操 我还要开呢
Fuck, i need that!
我它妈还要开呢
I fucking need that!
操!
Fuck you!
火线重案组 第二季 第五集 暗潮汹涌
The Wire S02E05 Undertow
* When you walk through the garden *
* You gotta watch your back *
* Well I beg your pardon *
* Walk the straight and narrow track *
* If you walk with Jesus *
* He's gonna save your soul *
* You gotta keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* He's got the fire and the fury *
* At his command *
* Well you don't have to worry *
* If you hold on to Jesus hand *
* We'll all be safe from Satan *
* When the thunder rolls *
* Just gotta help me keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* You gotta help me keep the devil *
"那以前是炼钢的吧?"  ---Spiros Vondas
为什么找我
Why me?
你不想加入
You don't want the posting,
我就找别人
I'll take someone else.
Valchek让我在他辖区里随便挑
Valchek gave me the pick of his district.
我不是说我不想干
I'm not saying i don't want it.
我只是想知道经过上次的事 你为什么还会找我
I'm asking why you would choose me after what happened last go around.
是啊 我也想过
Yeah, i thought about that, too.
看着东南区的警员名单 我对自己说
Looking down that list of names on the southeastern roster,I'm saying to myself:
"为什么要找一个出卖过你..."
"Why take a man who already burned you once...
"已经证明了自己不忠的人呢"
"Who already proved himself disloyal?"
你说 我为什么要这样做
Now, why would i do that?
我它妈的想不出来 警督
I have no fucking clue, lieutenant.
因为
Because
他被我抓到一次...
If i caught him once...
那他就应该不会再次犯混
He might be the last son of a bitch to try it twice.
我猜你上次已经足够内疚了...
I'm guessing you got enough shame from the last time...
应该不会再有第二次了
So that it won't happen again.
是的 长官 不会了
No, sir, it won't.
另外...
One other thing...
就我所知 你臂章上的杠子不是你应得的
As far as i'm concerned, those stripes on your sleeve aren't earned.
你虽然拿的是警司的薪水 但在专案组里...
Your paycheck may say "sergeant," but on this detail...
还是Greggs警探带领你们
Det. Greggs runs your team.
就跟以前一样
Same as it ever was.
怎样
Well?
算我一个
I'm in.
- 过来 你个小贱人 - 混--
- Come here, you sweet bitch. - Motherfu--
别拽我老二 兔爷
Don't be grabbing my dick, faggot.
我用无线电跟他联系了
I raised him on the radio.
他正赶过来
He's on his way in right now.
感激不尽 警官
Appreciate that, officer.
天气不错
Nice day.
银峰450型
Summit silver 450.
顶级烤肉架啊
Top of the line, right here.
在那边?
Over there?
嘿 Bubs
Yo, bubs.
水手Mcnulty?
Mcnulty, the sailor man?
注意船头
Watch the front.
给
Here.
帮我绑在那东西上面
Stick that on that thing there, will you?
系绳栓?
The cleat?
啥都不懂?
Ain't you know nothing?
看看你 可能只有我这么觉得
Look at you, i don't know, maybe it's just me... But
但这场面真有点不对劲
Something's way the fuck wrong with this picture.
那是啥玩意儿?
What the hell is that?
"巴尔的摩"结
A baltimore knot.
巴尔的摩结?
巴尔的摩结是什么鬼东西
What the hell is a baltimore knot?
不知道 但是从不打重样
I don't know, but it's never the same thing twice.
我能说什么呢 当警探的日子结束了
What can i tell you? My detecting days are over.
那你它妈的干嘛还让我找Omar?
What the fuck you have me hunt up omar then for?
那是老账了 记得Bird吗
That's old business. You remember bird?
他的案子下周开庭 Omar得出庭作证
His trial's up next week. Omar's got some witnessing to do.
他说你可以跟他用这个号码联系
He said you can reach him here at this number.
可以留口信
You can leave a message.
干得好 Bubs
Good work, bubs.
老规矩 给
As always. Here.
车马费
Cab fare.
好吧 呃...
Okay, um...
你说以牙还牙
You say tit-For-Tat,
我们打打法律的擦边球
And we let slide on a little county caper.
我不得不琢磨 你瞧
I got to think that, you know,
你得想想 你让我去完成的是什么活
You need to think about what you had me endeavoring to accomplish.
我是说 该死的 我不是去打探
I mean, what the fuck, man? I'm not out there asking about
随便什么无关紧要的货色
No random-Ass, who-Give-A-Damn nigger.
不 长官 你是在授意我
No, sir. I'm making inquiries in your behalf...
去找那个乖戾嚣张的混蛋Omar 伙计
In regards to that fucking unforgiving, motherfucking omar, man.
怎么说 他刁难你了?
Why? He play you hard?
我带着敬意去找他...
I go at him respectable...
他却拿把该死的枪指着我的脸
He put that goddamn shotgun in my face, man.
我就跟两根漆黑的枪管对视着
I'm looking at two tubes of the harbor tunnel staring right at me,
每根都贼粗
Each one about yea-Big.
我他妈的差点尿裤子...
I damn near pissed in my pants...
他就在那站着笑 幸灾乐祸
And he stood smiling like this shit is funny.
一点都不好玩
It ain't funny.
McNulty 我知道我是在"缴税"...
Mcnulty, i know i'm paying taxes on some things...
但我总觉得我不该只得到一个"干得好 Bubs"
I got to believe this is more aggregation than: "Good work, bubs,"
还有这么点小费
And a little bit of this.
补偿你的痛苦
For your pains.
我们的无名女尸查得怎么样了
Where are we at with the jane does?
查码头困难重重
Taking a hard look at the port,
我们得给每个在那船上做事的装卸工
We're gonna drop a grand jury summons on every stevedore
一张大陪审团的传票 敲山震虎
Who worked the ship, keep rattling cages.
跟我们共事的码头警察干得怎样
How's the port police broad working out for us?
她对码头挺了解的
She knows the docks okay.
可惜不是警探
No detective, though.
那样的话 你得增加人手
In that case, you need someone fresh.
Cole或者Massy 不管当班的谁
Cole, maybe, massy or whoever's up.
你今天得去东南区报到
You need to get over to the southeastern today.
暂调至专案组
You're detailed temporarily.
警监
Colonel,
警监 无意冒犯
Colonel, respectfully,
你就这么搞死我
Did you just fuck me over without giving me
却连半个破案的机会都不给?
Even half a chance to clear this case?
我们搞清楚 Freamon警探
Let's be clear, det. Freamon.
我想搞死你的时候 你会再清楚不过
When i fuck you over, you'll know it.
清楚到你不会问我这种傻冒问题
You'll be so goddamn certain, you won't need to ask the question.
而你 Moreland警探
And you, det. Moreland, are now
现在得独自面对14件无头案了
All alone with 14 red names.
有何感受?
How's it feel?
后面的停车坪
And the parking pad in the rear
在Federal Hill可是超值的
Is invaluable for federal hill.
平台上能看到港口景色?
The deck has a harbor view?
对 两个方向都可以
Yes, in two directions.
上去看看吧 你们会喜欢的
Go on up, take a look. I think you'll love it.
这里不是Federal Hill
This ain't federal hill.
- 对不起 你说什么 - 这里是Locust海角
- Excuse me? - This is the point, locust point.
就地产规划而言 Montgomery街以下...
As far as real estate goes, anything that is below montgomery street...
河道以上 都属Federal Hill
And above the water is now called federal hill.
你们俩要买房子吗
Are you two house hunting?
刚开始找
We just started.
如果你们对这片地区有兴趣 我可以给你们列个清单
If you're interested in this area, i could run some listings for you.
这间特别的房子...
This particular house--
是我Treesey阿姨的
Is my aunt treesey's.
真的 你阿姨?
Really, your aunt?
她是Mcdonald家的亲戚么
Ls she a relation to the mcdonalds?
不 她是我亲戚
Nope. She's a relation to me.
她大约四年前过世
She died, like, four years ago.
她家人之后就把房子转手了
The family sold the house right after.
这是标价吗
Is that the price?
对 这是挂牌价
That's the listing, yes.
他们不会真要那么高的价吧?
They ain't gonna get that much, right?
这我说不好
I can't say for certain,
但在1200号跟这房子类似的那套 上周卖了34万
But one just like it in the 1200 block sold for $340,000 last week.
34万?
$340,000?
-谢谢 -不客气
-Thanks. -Yeah.
也许我们该租房
Maybe we should rent.
我们来这是因为Valchek...
We're here because valchek wants us here...
因为他相信这个人和他的穷酸工会...
Because he believes this man and his down-At-The-Heels union local...
荷包太鼓了
Has too much money.
作为起步
To start with,
你跟Freamon给工会 办公楼电话安上窃听器
You and freamon are gonna put some dnrs on the union hall phones.
另外 尽你们所能调查工会
Also, run what you can on the union
财政情况和Sobotka个人的
Finances and on sobotka personally.
我们整合一下
We put that together,
交给警长 向他证明我们在查...
Copy it to the major to show him we're on it...
多争取一点时间
And buy ourselves a little time.
同时 你们仨使出浑身解数
Meanwhile, you three, do what you do best.
搞清楚码头工周末狂欢的时候 喜欢在哪买毒品...
Find out where port folks like to cop on a friday night...
安排几次抓捕 也许来一两次卧底诱捕
Set up some hand-To-Hands, maybe a reverse or two.
码头有很多是白人 对吧
A lot of these port guys re white, aren't they?
我是说 还包括一些东南区的街头毒贩
Mean, some of the southeast street dealers, too.
所以你们该出动个白人...
So that means you're gonna need a white boy...
到东南区的街角转悠 对吗
To go down to some of these southeastern corners, right?
所以Kima和Carv上屋顶
So kima, carv on the rooftops.
该我上前线了
It's my time to front.
让你们看看我的表现 兄弟们
I'll show you how it's done, homes.
酷哥Lester 顺利报道
Cool lester smooth.
进来如何?
What's happening?
同一个烂专案组同一帮操蛋的家伙...
Same fuck-Ups in the same shit detail...
在同一个厕所样的办公室干活
Working out of the same shithouse kind of office.
你们真没点长进 明白吗
You people lack for personal growth, you know that?
这是个临时任命
It's a temporary posting.
行动结束Rawls就会把你调回去
Rawls gets you back at the end of the run.
如果他还要我的话
If he wants me.
我最近上了他黑名单
Last i looked, i was high on his shit list.
那我们倒是帮了你啊
Then we did you a favor.
我不会说得那么绝对
I wouldn't go that far.
去他的 我们要查谁
But fuck it. Who we chasing?
Frank Sobotka?
Frank sobotka?
瞧他多牛
How fucking good is he?
你认识他?
You know the man?
我和Bunk Moreland上周 还在跟这帮人周旋...
Me and bunk moreland were fucking with this guy last week...
查那件集装箱女尸案
Working that case about dead girls in the container.
他是嫌疑人?
He a suspect?
不算 只能说是个清楚码头那些勾当的人
No, just someone who know what's getting done on the port terminals.
- 你们查他干嘛 - 我岳父恨他入骨
- Why are you on him? - My father-In-Law hates his guts.
这在东南区无人不晓
Which, in the southeastern, goes for probable cause.
Valchek认为他钱包太鼓
Valchek thinks he has too much cash.
所以你们认为是毒品?
So you're thinking drugs?
在这破地方 还能犯什么别的罪?
In this fucking town, what other crime is there?
你知道我本可以早点过来
You know i would've been down here sooner,
只是Terrell正好病了...
It's just with terrell being sick and all....
但是 Dee
But, dee,
我衣食无忧
I got everything we need paid for.
等你出来
When you come home,
Stringer会让你做些别的生意
Stringer's saying they gonna hook you up with something out of the mix.
比如开个夜总会
Like running a club,
或其他一些正经生意
Or straight business, like.
String说他们不会再让你卷进去
String say they gonna keep you apart from it...
让你有多些时间照顾家里
And give back some time for family.
为了你 为了我 也为了Terrell
For you and me and terrell.
家?
Family?
他们正在考虑能为你做点什么
They thinking about how they can do for you.
即便知道你跟你叔叔在冷战...
They making all these plans...
他们还是想了很多办法
Even though you been playing cold with your uncle.
至少Stringer是这么说的
Stringer says so, anyhow.
你干嘛要这样
Why you be like that?
他们想着法子帮你 你却拒之千里?
Throwing them off when they looking to do for you?
他们只是用所谓的"我们是一家人 一切都为爱"利用你
They playing you with that "we're family, and it's all about love."
他们就是这么干的
That's how they do.
等到你没有利用价值了 就也不谈什么狗屁家人
When they got no more use for you, that family shit disappears.
一切只为生意 Donette
It's just about business, donette.
Dee 他们会帮我们的
Dee, they gonna be there for us.
怎么样 伙计? 这能搞到"死亡之握"
What's up, man? You got that death grip.
把钱给Stony就好了
You know stony got that check.
走慢点 白痴 我是说你得在这把钱给了
Slow down, fool. I'm saying you need to spend that shit here.
"死亡之握"给力着呢
Death grip be the fucking bomb, yo.
- 我才不要 - 这操蛋的说货不好
- I ain't got no ends. - Motherfucker said it ain't shit.
不 我没说
No, i ain't say that.
嘿 够了 放开那小子
That's enough, yo, let that shit be.
- 操你全家 - 哦 混球?
- Fuck you all. - Yeah, motherfucker?
嘿 B
Yo, b.
里头出事了
Shit jumping off in the pit, yo.
该死
Damn.
那算是怎么回事
What the fuck was that?
毒鬼抹黑我们的货 说"死亡之握"屁都不如
Fiend badmouthing our shit, saying death grip ain't all that.
就因为他说了句实话 就打他了?
Now we're beating niggers over speaking the truth?
我又没动手 那些小弟干的
I ain't hit him, the young'uns, yo.
没法跟那些傻帽讲道理
You can't tell these fools nothing.
我们在用些破烂欺行霸市
We stomping niggers over bullshit, man.
该有人让Stringer管管这事了
Somebody got to pull stringer up on this.
Zig 怎么了
Zig, what's up?
老天 zig 发生什么事了
Jesus, zig, what the fuck happened?
我被那些操蛋黑鬼逮住了
Fucking niggers got me.
什么
What?
抢了我的钱 还把我的爱车开走了
Took my money, and they got princess, too.
听懂了吗 他们把我车开走了!
You hear me? They got my fucking car.
如果我有枪 我对天发誓
If i had a gun, i swear to god I would've capped
每人都来一枪子儿
Every one of those motherfuckers.
- 你报警了? - 不行
- You call the cops? - Can't.
是毒资
It was over some dope.
你倒卖他们的毒品 是不是
You bought a fucking package, didn't you?
是不是
Didn't you?!
你活该倒霉 傻逼
Serves you right, you stupid fuck.
找谁买的
From who?
"麦克白"?
White mike?
那个叫Cheese的黑佬 在Wolfe和Ashland街混的
This nigger cheese, up on wolfe and ashland.
- 就几盎司 - 干嘛不找"麦克白"?
- A few ounces, you know? - Why not white mike?
去他的 你也知道他是什么人
Fuck mike, you know how he be.
我他妈怎么知道?
Why the fuck would i know how he be?
Nicky
Nicky,
那又不是我的错 不是
It ain't my fault, all right? It ain't.
你看 生意有点冷清
Look, business has been slow,
货还没倒卖出去
Package ain't turned around yet.
但那帮榆木脑袋就是听不进去
But the fucking hoodleheads ain't hearing it,
所以扁了我一顿
So i get jumped.
开走我的爱车 扣着她换赎金
They got princess, man. They're holding her for fucking ransom.
现在他们告诉我...
And now they're telling me...
说如果我到周五不把钱交出来 他们就要干掉我
They're telling me if i don't have the money by friday, they're going to kill me.
我需要2700块
I need $2,700.
然后呢
So?
你是毒贩 那它妈的去卖啊
You're a drug dealer, go sell some fucking drugs.
你搞砸了那批货是吧 Zig?
You fucked up the package, didn't you, zig?
我不会给你钱的
I ain't giving you the money.
他们会杀了我
They're gonna kill me.
我的钱给Aimee了
I gave my money to aimee
租了公寓
For an apartment.
交了押金和购置些家具
Security deposit and some furniture over at littlepages.
我不会拿来给你的 Zig
I ain't got it for you, zig.
这帮瘪三
You cocksuckers.
圣地亚哥
进来
Yeah?
警长 我们将对码头进行些诱捕
- Major we're about to make some hand-To-Hands around the port.
Daniels警督让我来问问看 有没有监视车
Lt. Daniels said i should see you about a surveillance van.
监视车?
The van?
那辆车借给西南区了
The van's on loan to the southwest.
好吧
Okay.
敢玩我 走着瞧吧
Fuck with my ass, will you?
又回到了我们的老朋友这
Bringing us back to our old friends,
供给和需求
Supply and demand.
好了
All right,
你们的研究论文在这
Your research papers are here.
记得周五的回家考试
Remember friday, take-Home test.
写得不错 Bell先生
Well done, mr. Bell.
Lucas先生 能给我五分钟吗
Mr. Lucas, you got five minutes?
没问题
Absolutely.
有个问题也许你能帮帮我
There's something maybe you can help me out with.
我尽力
I'll try.
在一个竞争激烈的市场 你手头只有些劣等品...
What are the options when you got an inferior product...
该作何选择
In an aggressive marketplace?
如果你占有较大的市场份额
If you have a large share of the market,
你可以并购竞争对手
You can buy up the competition.
如果没有呢
And if you don't?
降价以争取更大的市场份额
Reduce price to increase market share.
那得降低经常性开支
That assumes low overhead.
当然 否则你就要遭受损失...
Of course, otherwise, you operate at a loss...
或者更遭
And worse,
你的价格降了...
As your prices drop...
你的产品最终失去了顾客的信任
Your product eventually loses consumer credibility.
你知道
You know,
世通公司的新CEO也刚面临了这种窘境
The new ceo of worldcom was faced with this very problem.
指2002年WorldCom 90亿的财务诈骗案
公司被牵扯到史上最大的一场诈骗案中
The company was linked to one of the largest fraud cases in history.
- 因此他提出... - 改名?
- So he proposed-- - To change the name?
正是(后WorldCom改名为MCI)
Exactly.
哪个?
Which one?
手上拿着小香肠的就是
He's got a weenie in his hand.
这么说 不正是你吗?
On this case, ain't that you?
Thomas Pakusa
Thomas pakusa,
来看看
Come on down.
什么玩意
What the fuck is that?
大陪审团传票
Grand jury summons.
大陪审团?
Grand jury?
你骗我们 只是伤了我们的心
You lie to us, you hurt our feelings.
骗他们 就是伪证罪了
You lie to them, it's perjury.
还有一张我刚给了你外面的烤肉师傅
And one more i just dropped on your barbecue chef outside.
你以前要有趣得多 知道吗 Bea?
You used to be a lot more fun, you know that, bea?
我身后这位就是John Spamanato
That's john spamanato right there.
Johnny "Fifty"
Johnny fifty.
很高兴认识你 警官
How you doing, officer?
Johnny Fifty?
Johnny fifty?
那是啥玩意儿?
What the fuck is that?
臭小子在他25岁生日时喝了53杯啤酒
Son of a bitch drinks 53 beers on his 25th birthday.
如此这般
So as to be,
你们怎么说来着 诗意地
What do you call it, poetical,
就这么称呼他了
We rounded it off.
"Baltimore市巡回法庭大陪审团"
"Grand jury for the circuit court of baltimore city."
你为Atlantic Light号接过活 对吧
You worked the atlantic light, right?
上过船的每个人都要作证
Everybody on that ship testifies.
做什么证
About what?
关于集装箱女尸的证词
About them girls in the can.
这位探长认为我们对那破事略知一二
The detective here thinks we know something about that mess.
他怀疑我们把她们扔在码头上...
He thinks we'd leave them there on the dock...
装在集装箱里 让她们在黑暗中死去...因为...
In a box, dying there in the dark because....
究竟是因为什么呢 警探?
Because why, detective?
有什么原因非要让那些女孩死于非命?
What reason would we have to want girls to die like that?
如果我们知情
Why would any of us leave them in there
又为什么要把她们留在那?
If we knew anything about it?
我有老婆
I got a wife
还有三个姐妹
And three sisters.
她们还有女儿
And they got daughters.
我对女子相当尊敬
And i got too much respect for women
所以才没因你脑中的想法大发雷霆
Not to be pissed off at what's in your heads right now.
码头有那么多集装箱 你偏偏就丢了那个
Of all the cans on the terminal, that's the one you lose in the stacks.
该死 我们全不知情
We didn't know shit, goddamn it!
你想让我们见大陪审团 见就是了
You want us to dance with a grand jury, we will!
你怎么说 Johnny?
What do you say, johnny?
对那些问题你怎么回答
What do you say to any question?
我谨遵第五戒律(十戒中的不杀生)
I take the fifth commandment.
如果他们豁免你 让你指证你工会兄弟呢
And if they offer you immunity to testify against your union brothers?
- 我不记得了 - 不记得什么
- I don't remember. - Don't remember what?
什么都不记得
Nothing.
你别忘了
What you're forgetting
东海岸的每个工会兄弟...
Is that every i.B.S. Iocal on the east coast...
都和联邦大陪审团打过几次照面了
Has had its ass in front of a federal grand jury two or three times already.
你们要发传票 发就是了
You want to throw your summonses? Throw them.
你想查我们的记录? 用不着传票
You want to subpoena our records? You don't need a subpoena no more.
我们的账目八年前就对司法部公开了
Our books were open to the justice department for eight years.
我们挺过了"Bobby" Kennedy"(曾任司法部长)
We're here through bobby kennedy,
Tricky Dick" Nixon...(曾任总统)
tricky dick nixon...
"工会破坏者"Ronnie Reagan(曾任美国总统)
Ronnie "the union buster" reagan,
还有其他几个狗娘养的
And half a dozen other sons of bitches.
我们也能挺过你们这件屁事
We'll be here through your weak bullshit, no problem!
这四个今天不上班
These four ain't working today.
你把传票留下...
You wanna leave the papers here...
我会转交给他们让他们进城
I'll make sure they get them and go downtown on them.
走吧
Come on.
- 今天? - 马上
- Today? - Now!
你描述杀害Gant先生的武器...
You described the weapon used to kill mr. Gant...
是点三八半自动手枪
As a.380 semi-Automatic.
你提供了型号 甚至是制造商
You provided the size, and even suggested the manufacturer:
"澳大利亚 或某个以A开头的国家"
"Australian, or one of those 'a' countries."
对吗
Is that correct?
没错
Indeed.
而你离凶手大约50尺?
And you were approximately 50 feet from the shooter?
对 女士
Yes, ma'am,
你知道 多少有点误差
You know, give or take.
Little先生 在那种距离下
Mr. Little, at that distance
你怎能辨认出凶器的制造商呢
How were you able to determine who manufactured the weapon?
不能
I wasn't.
那你是怎么提供这个信息给警探的?
Then how were you able to relate that information to the detectives?
Bird给我看过
Bird showed it to me.
他在谋杀前给你看过凶器?
He showed you the weapon before the murder?
我们说的是哪次谋杀
Which murder we talking?
Bird还有别的谋杀案?
Bird committed more than one murder?
狗改不了吃屎 知道我的意思吧
Fish got to swim, you know what i'm saying?
就像我之前说的 Bird见人就秀他的手枪...
Like i said before, bird was showing that thing to everybody...
胡吹他的丰功伟绩
Talking about this deed and the next.
在你们找上我查他之前
I didn't pay him no mind until
我对他根本不以为意
You all came and showed him some interest.
Little先生
Mr. Little, if you
希望你不介意在外面等几分钟 我想和McNulty私下聊聊
If you wouldn't mind waiting outside I'd like a few words with officer mcnulty.
我认为他干得不错
I thought he did good.
想象一下让那个反社会者出庭作证
Imagine the mileage maury levy gets out of me
会给Maury Levy多少口实
Putting that sociopath on the stand.
你得承认 上庭就不同了
You got to admit, it'll be different.
至少让他穿正式点
Dress him up at least.
我可不能让他穿那样出庭
I can't have him on the stand looking like that.
拿着去买上庭穿的衣服
Here's a voucher for court clothes.
要能配领带的
Anything with a tie.
我是说 Dirt...
I'm saying, dirt...
相当我手下 就得好好跟着干
You wanna be my nigger, you got to be with me for real.
听懂了吗
You see what i'm saying, yo?
知道 我会的
Well, i'll be.
我一直跟你说 要站好自己的岗
All the time i be telling you, be on post.
但是该死的 哥们
But damn, homes,
可你整天就围着群婊子
You all the time up in some damn
窝在那里"扮家家"
Crib trying to play house with them bitches.
我是说 我要有事不得不离开...
I'm saying, you all be seriously fucked up because i'm out here...
你就死定了
Getting done what needs done.
明白吗 小子?
Feel me, nigga?
无赖小偷啥都敢偷 不是吗
Thieving motherfuckers take everything, don't they?
知道我在说什么吧 Dirt
You know what i'm saying, dirt.
你要做我手下 就得好好干
You wanna be my nigger, you gots to deliver for real.
情况如何 Charlie?
How'd we do, charlie?
我快能让一个家伙发誓
I've almost got one of them ready to swear
码头就在水边了
That the docks are actually near the water.
那些家伙不吃这套
They don't scare, them guys.
现在怎么办
What now?
你说你在那一个二五仔都没有吗?
You telling me you never had a ci down there, right?
二五仔?
A cl?
线人
An informant.
你在码头没线人?
You ain't got no informants on the dock?
一个你可以找上门的人? 一个跟你有过交情的人?
Someone you could go to on this? Someone you got a history with?
难怪说警察充其量 就看他线人的苗头
They say a police is only as good as his informants.
就是说我们实在不咋地
Meaning, we ain't about much.
凭单面额150块
The voucher says $150.
看看甩卖区
Look on the clearance rack.
- 看上去不错 - 才不是
- It's a look. - No, it ain't.
也对
Yeah.
你自己找吧
You figure it out for yourself.
我要去街对面的联邦大楼
I'm going across the street to the federal building.
大约半小时后见
I'll see you in about a half-Hour.
听着 伙计 要不是来这 我就在是在去Howard街了
Look, man, if i ain't here, i'm round the way on howard street,
Liddell店
Liddell's.
或者跟Muffy泡在俱乐部里
Either that, or i'll be with muffy at the club.
他上哪去了
Where's he at?
他说要去拿些装备
Said he had to go get his props.
1208呼叫
12-08.
1208请说
请求与1210联络
Request lateral with 12-10.
总台 他可以和我在六台通话
Kga, he can meet me on 6.
- 收到吗 1208? - 收到 第六频道
- Do you copy, 12-08? - 10-4, on 6.
嘿 呆瓜 你上哪去了
Yo, dickhead, where you been at?
要做卧底时 Carv
When you're working deep cover, carv,
你得融入角色
You got to get into the part.
- 怎么样 - 有什么能帮你的
- What's up? - You need a little help?
也许吧 哥们
Maybe, bro.
你这有生货吗?
You got any raw up in here?
带钱了吗
You got it to spend?
当然
For sure.
好吧 成交 过去找我的手下
All right, then we good. Go and holler at my niggers round back.
好的
All right
嘿 Carv
Yo, carv.
收到吗
You copy this?
万事俱备 宝贝 万事俱备(包括他手里的牙签)
It's all in the props, baby. All in the props.
移民局
国土安全局
看出什么区别吗
Feel any different?
我也没看出来 我是Cleary特工
Me neither. Special agent cleary.
Jim McNulty 市警的
Jim mcnulty, from the city.
有什么能帮你的
How can i help you?
Key桥落水的浮尸
Found floating off the key bridge.
我们认为她与
We think she's linked to the dead girls
Patapsco河畔的集装箱女尸案有联系
Found in the container at patapsco.
你们的人刚来过
Your people were just here,
想查那个集装箱
Asking for a trace on the can.
凶杀科的
Homicide fellows.
- 黑人 Moreland和Freamon? - 对
- Black guys, moreland, freamon? - Yeah,
- 你跟他们共事? - 算是吧
- You working with them? - Sort of,
是我把她捞上来的 觉得有责任找到她的家人
I fished her out. I kind of feel like it's on me to find her people.
你在开玩笑吧
You're kidding, right?
不 我在想你们会不会 你瞧...
No, i thought maybe if you guys have, you know...
抓过一些被送来巡回卖淫的女子
Been pulling in any women who've been over here on the circuit.
走进我的世界吧 Virginia
Step into my world, virginia.
大陪审团?
A grand jury?
他们抓了几个我们的人
They snatched up some of our guys,
带他们到市区
Drove them downtown.
但你们一无所知
But you know nothing.
当然 我们什么都不知道
Yeah, no shit, we know nothing.
那天唯一一个知道
The only guy they got that even knows
你们有个集装箱的 就是"马面"
You had a can that day was horse...
但他屁都不会放一个
And he ain't gonna say shit to nobody.
你确定?
You sure?
"马面"硬得很
Horse is a rock.
不用担心他
Don't ever worry about him.
也不用担心我叔叔
My uncle neither.
但你说他想不干了
But you say he wants to stop.
嗯 短期内
Yeah, for a little while.
他想停止你通过我们的码头运集装箱...
He wants you to stop moving cans through our docks...
至少等风声过去
At least until this shit chills.
查的是本地警方 对吧
These were local police, right?
对
Yeah.
他们只关注那些女孩
Their interest is in the girls.
事情发生在船上 而船已经开走了
That happened on the ship, the ship is gone.
死胡同一条
A dead end.
他们想找的混蛋
The malaka they want,
已经在费城 栽在我们手里
We already got to in philly.
又是一个"死"胡同
Another dead end.
警察什么也查不到
The police are going nowhere.
不过...
But,
更重要的是
More important,
我们会打消Frank的担心
We address frank's concerns.
告诉你叔叔我想见他
You tell your uncle i will meet with him.
他说他想见"希腊人"
He says he wants to meet with the greek.
他想跟"希腊人"说什么
Anything he can say to the greek,
跟我说就行了
He can say to me.
他说他想见"希腊人"
Says he wants the greek.
你告诉他时间地点
Says you tell him when and where.
Niko
Niko.
另一桩买卖...
About that other business,
那些化学品....
The chemicals....
你要那些东西干什么
What do you need them for?
就是桩买卖
It's just business.
我们间只有交易
Everything is just business with us.
五分钱买
Buy for a nickel,
一毛钱卖
You sell for a dime.
是吗
Yeah?
谁会想只价值一毛的化学品?
Who wants a dime's worth of fucking chemicals?
这么说 这些只是这个办事处 掌握的无证外侨?
So these are undocumenteds from just this field office?
只有Maryland州和Delaware州的
Maryland and delaware only.
当中有没有还被扣着的?
Any of them still in your custody?
我想给她们看看照片 碰碰运气
I'd love the chance to show some photos, maybe get lucky.
那本里的都已经被驱逐出境了
Everyone in that book was deported.
想想也知道 有些又跑回来了
You can guess, some of them are already back.
哪个驻地会有目前在拘的?
Any field office have anything active?
我这正在查
That's what i'm looking at right here.
圣地亚哥那刚抓了一批女孩
You got some girls in custody in san diego,
西雅图也有
Also seattle.
有没有我能直接开车去的地方?
Anything i can drive to?
最近的是新泽西州Hudson郡
Closest is a case up in jersey, hudson county.
四天前突击了几个俱乐部 拘留了12人
Raid on a couple clubs up there put 12 in their bullpen four days ago.
那里可以
That'll work.
这么说你真要在私人时间去那?
So you really gonna go up there on your own time?
对 花一天去看看
I'll take a day, yeah.
你和这女的到底什么关系?
What's between you and this girl?
你知道停尸间是
You seen what happens down at the morgue,
怎么处理无名尸的吗
When they can't id a body?
我见过
I have.
Mau
Mau.
最近可好
How you been?
老样子
Same old.
是吗
Yeah?
你有工时了?
You getting some days?
还挺多的
Pretty much.
我现在在塔台
I'm in the tower now,
指挥航道
Working the lanes.
你要进来吗
You want to come in?
我这有 我不知道 啤酒
I got, i don't know, some beers,
可能还有些巴卡第鸡尾酒
Maybe some bacardi around.
也许我们可以去外面 边喝咖啡边谈?
Maybe we could just go for a cup of coffee and talk, you know?
我拿件外套
Let me get my jacket.
我跟他说 "Dee 你为什么要那样"
So i tell him, "dee, why you acting like that?"
他只是干坐在那 好像我什么都没说
He just sit there like i didn't say a damn thing.
若无其事一样
He off the damn hook.
你跟他说过那些安排吧?
You tell him about the plans, right?
我告诉他你们会为他打理好一切
I told him you all was gonna set him up and everything.
他也知道 在他离开的时候 你们怎么照顾我的
And he know how you all been doing for me while he away.
其中一部分
He knows some.
我是说 该死 不用让他知道全部 对吧
I mean, damn, he don't need to know about it all, right?
无论如何
Anyway,
我说我下周末再去看他...
I'm saying i'll get down there next weekend...
但他看着我就像我什么也没说
And he look at me like i ain't saying shit.
他说让他自己待着
He say just leave him alone.
该给烤肉翻面了
Got to turn that roast.
给你瞧瞧 String 真的
You gonna see, string, for real.
Donette也会厨艺
Little donette know how to burn.
你老爸和我们作对 小家伙
Your father bucking us, little man.
你说该怎么办
What you think about that?
嗯 你说得对
Yeah. I think you're right.
操蛋的Ziggy
Fucking ziggy, man.
要我为他的破事吃枪子儿?
I'm about to get my ass shot behind his bullshit?
我们讲理 他们也讲理
We're reasonable, they're reasonable.
放屁 也许在你那里是吧
Fuck that, maybe on your side of town.
什么事
What's up?
我们为辆车来见个人
Came to see a man about a car.
你可以告诉Cheese我们来了
Maybe tell cheese we're here.
嘿 Cheese
Yo, cheese.
白仔
White boy.
嘿 你带钱来了吗 伙计?
Yo, you got my money, man?
我们就是来谈这个的
That's what we came to talk about.
你倒是挺够胆的...
Yo, you got to a lot of heart...
来这却不带钱
Coming up in here without my fucking money.
我们认为我们能找出解决的办法...
We thought maybe we can work something out...
让你拿到你想要的
So you can get what's yours.
你们准备怎么做
How you plan to do that?
你把车还来
You give the car back,
我会让他把车卖了
I'll get him to sell it off.
Camaro (大黄蜂)配了350引擎
Camaro with a 350 in it,
转手的话不只3000块
It's got to be worth more than $3,000.
真聪明
That's right clever.
不得不说 真聪明
Right clever, i got to say.
我很感激你们大老远跑过来...
And i appreciate you all coming all this way so much...
我会多给那小鬼一周时间付钱
I'll give the boy another week to pay.
当然
Of course,
那车是绝值不了3000块了
That ride ain't worth nothing near $3,000.
你不相信我?
You don't believe me?
看看
Have a look.
幸福就是做Ziggy
你出现在我门前 我还以为会有好事呢
You show up at my door, i'm thinking better thoughts than this.
你吃准了是吧?
And you counted on that?
那我还能找谁呢?
Who else am i gonna ask?
我不是个告密者 Beadie
I ain't no snitch, beadie.
即使为了你也不行
Not even for you am i a snitch.
我不这么想
I'm not thinking about it like that.
我是想
I'm thinking,
有这么个人
Here's a guy, and
我们在一起过 虽然 你知道
We had some times together and even though, you know,
最终没能得到他想要的结果...
It didn't get to where he might have wanted it...
他仍然是个我能跟他谈这事的好人
He's still a good guy someone i can talk to about this.
怎么会最终没结果的
How come it didn't go nowhere?
你做得很好了 谁知道呢
You did good. Who knows?
我不知道
I don't know,
天知道
You never know.
我可以给你看看她们死亡的照片
I could show you pictures of how they died.
残缺的指甲 壁上的血迹
Broken fingernails, blood on the walls.
突然之间 你又成了警察了
All of a sudden, you're a cop.
帮帮我 Mau
Help me with this, mau.
你们抓了"马面"和其他人 但什么也没审出来 对吧
You didn't get shit from grabbing up horseface and them, did you?
这么想还挺有趣的
It's kind of funny when you think about it.
我是说 你跟个无头苍蝇似地乱窜...
I mean, you running around like your head's all chopped off...
想找人提供你线索...
Iooking for someone to clue you in...
可是你想知道的那些...
When a lot of what you're asking about...
其实近在咫尺
Is right there for the taking.
怎么可能?
How so?
过去我们检验员用纸笔记录 对吧?
Used to be us checkers did everything with paper and a pencil, right?
货船的所有动向
Every move on a ship,
我们都写在纸上
We wrote it down.
货船离开后
When that ship sails,
不再有问题 这些纸就会被扔掉
And there ain't no problems then that paper gets tossed.
现在不这么干了 不是吗
That don't happen today, right?
什么资料都不会扔掉
Nothing gets tossed anymore.
电脑
The computer.
谢谢 Mau
Thanks, mau.
怎么样
Well?
一个好消息一个坏消息 Zig
Good news and bad, zig.
那帮该死的黑鬼
Those fucking niggers.
先说坏消息吧
Give me the bad.
他们还是会杀你
They're still gonna kill you.
会再等上一个星期
They're gonna wait a week.
那还能有啥好消息?
What the fuck can be good?
你可以退掉汽车险了
You can cancel your car insurance.
两管红帽
Let me get two red tops.
来了
There we go.
希望你们都记了笔记
I hope you guys are taking notes.
给你
Two caps, yo.
靠
Shit.
"一加一"
One-And-One.
他再给我叼牙签 我就要用它戳他眼睛了
One more time with that toothpick, i'm going to stab his eye with it.
好意思当自己是希腊人 居然把这叫饭
Ashamed he should be to be greek and call this a diner.
跟他谈谈能安抚他
A talk would ease his mind.
先安抚我吧
Ease my mind first.
这生意扯上大陪审团了
This business with the grand jury.
我们去法院打探了 没什么特别的
We checked the courthouse. There is nothing special.
不过是些例行询问
Just the regular panels.
他们想吓唬那些码头工人
They're trying to scare the men on the docks.
- 结果呢? - 没人开口
- And? - Nobody talks.
但Sobotka
But sobotka,
就像我说的 他很不爽
As i said, he's upset.
这事的动静比他想的要大
It is more attention than he expected.
他得要钱请律师
He will need money for his lawyers.
给他加倍的钱
Double his fee.
但我不用去见他
But i don't need to meet with him.
用钱说话吧
Let the money talk.
我们从Atlanta弄来的货都不行了
Everything we get from atlanta been walked on.
一个比一个差
Each one weaker than the other.
那个Roberto(纽约的毒贩)眼下还在跟我们避嫌
And this nigger roberto is on the shelf to us right now.
我是说 要维持高楼区的生意越来越难...
I mean, it's getting hard to hold onto the towers...
我们的货已经垄断不了市场了
Without our name all over the product is what i'm saying.
谁手头有好货?
Who got the good shit?
东区
Eastside.
东区的谁
Eastside, who?
Milton有一小部分
This nigger milton got a small cut,
"Prop" Joe...
Prop joe...
牙买加人盘踞了整条街 知道我在说谁吗
This jamaican cat who got the strip off gay street.
你说的是Petey...Petey Dixon
You talking about petey, petey dixon.
你午餐时间上高速...
You go over to the expressway at lunchtime...
- 你就会看见那些瘾君子从西跑到东 - 该死
- You can watch the fiends traveling from west to east. - Damn!
我是说 我在用垃圾偷工减料
I mean, i'm cutting shit with shit right now,
但骗得了一时 骗不了一世
Trying to cheat, but sooner or later.
我明白 我在想办法
I hear you, man, i'm on it.
你跟Dee的关系缓和了吗
You working it out with dee?
那孩子总会想通的
Boy got to find his own way.
我是说 我们该继续笼络这孩子
I'm saying, you know I think we should keep reaching out to this kid.
给他和他女友点东西
Give something to him and his girl. I don't know,
让他们知道我们在想办法
Show them we got a plan.
把一些产业置于他名下
Take some real estate, put it in dee's name.
好让他自由后有个依靠
He has something to come home to.
就这么办
Do it.
String 事已至此 你懂我意思吧?
Thing is, string, what happened happened, you know what i mean?
该下决定了
Push come to shove,
我待他不薄 不是吗
I've been fair to him, ain't l?
你很够意思了
You've been fair.
有点过头了
Too fair.
"希腊人"呢
Where's the greek?
他让我过来
He sent me.
去你的 操他娘
Fuck you, and fuck him.
Frank
Frank,
他让我过来跟你说 我们给你双倍的钱...
He sent me to tell you that we're doubling your fee...
帮你渡过法律难关
To help with any legal troubles.
他还让我告诉你
He also told me to tell you that
他很抱歉因我们的行为
He regrets that you're still having problems
让你身陷麻烦
On our behalf.
警察到处抓我的人...
They're throwing my people in back of police cars...
这混蛋却不肯出来当面谈谈?
And this asshole can't even talk face to face?
到此为止
I'm done.
老子不玩了 我要跟你们划清界限
I'm out. I need nothing more to do with you people.
我不要钱也不惹麻烦 还有个工会指望我呢
I don't need the trouble or the money. I got a union to run.
那以前是炼钢的吧
They used to make steel there, no?
那些冒烟的烟囱
Smoke from the stacks.
可惜那里面...
But inside....
高锰酸钾
Potassium permanganate.
"高锰酸"怎么写
Spell "permanganate."
F-U-C-K
F-U-C-K.
你居然也懂这一手 Zig?
You even know what the fuck you're doing there, zig?
我也是检查员分会的 不是吗?
I'm in the checker's local, right?
你知道 47分会的小子们...
You know, while you local 47 boys...
还在跟散装货较劲时
Were having bulk cargo dropped on your heads...
我们早就与时俱进了
We was out grabbing the future by the balls.
于是你只要在那上面打打字
So you just type that shit in there
就能找到答案?
And ask it for an answer?
我问你
Let me ask you:
我们为什么要关心他们用那个来干嘛
Why do we give a fuck what the shit is for?
他们想要就要吧
If they want it, they want it.
除此之外 如果我不赶快弄到钱...
I mean, besides, if i don't get some money soon...
就要死翘翘了
I'm fucking toasted.
从古柯叶中提炼可卡因所需化学品
我不知道你们听谁说的
I don't know who you've been talking to but
我们这现在没有那种盗窃了
We don't have that kind of stealing going on down here.
不像以前了
It's not like the old days.
是吗
No?
这里那里总会有一两起 但
A little here and there, but
新技术改变了一切
For the most part the new technology has changed everything.
- 看见这儿的小箱子了吗 - 别乱指
- Look, see this little box right here? - You fucking mind?
Ring压力有点大...
Ring's a little stressed right now...
他把本该昨天送到Jessup批发市场的...
Having misplaced a frozen can full of japanese tuna steaks...
一整箱冰冻日本金枪鱼排放错了地方
Supposed to be at the jessup wholesale market by yesterday.
咬我啊
Bite me.
Frank 这些警官是...
Frank, these officers are--
我知道他们是谁
I know who they are.
Frank帮着建立了这个系统
Frank here helped set this system up.
他恐怕能比我解释得更好
He probably can explain it better than i can,
- 如果他不介意的话 - 不介意 头儿
- If he doesn't mind. - No problem, chief.
简而言之
In a nutshell,
这儿显示的...
What this shows...
是4号平台的船
Is the aqua verde at berth 4.
安排85次搬运 包括货柜
The plan calls for 85 moves. That's cans,
集装箱 一些卸下船 一些上船
Containers, coming off the ship, and others going back on.
现在看这屏幕 每次一个集装箱上下船
Now, look at the screen. Every time a can goes on or off,
电脑都会创建记录 并存入永久数据库
The computer creates a record and puts it in the permanent database.
他刚刚说有了电脑 从码头偷集装箱就变困难了
He was saying the computer makes it hard to steal off the docks.
那我们的码头经理有没有告诉你
Did our port manager tell you that
目前为止仅仅Patapsco站 我们就丢了160个集装箱?
Right now we got 160 boxes missing off the patapsco terminal alone?
又或者上次盘点汽车底盘时 发现少了300个?
Or that last time we inventoried the truck chassis we came up 300 light?
不 我想没说吧 这就是经营管理了
No, i suppose not. That's management for you.
160?
也不全是偷的 也可能是意外遗失
Not that all of them are stolen. You can lose a can by accident,
没什么大不了的 首先
No problem. For one thing,
是这些手持设备 用的是无线电
These hand-Helds use radio waves.
外面有那么多集装箱和设备
With all the equipment and container stacks out there sometimes
无线电会被屏蔽 这时有发生 一些集装箱不会被登记
Waves get knocked down. That happens, a can don't get entered.
又或者 只是检验员犯了个错误
Or, just as easy, a checker makes the wrong entry.
要么因为他太懒
Either 'cause he's lazy,
办事马虎 要么他宿醉未醒
he's sloppy, or he's still shitfaced from the night before.
或者 更简单的可能是 你手指太粗
Or, simpler than that, you got fat fingers.
无意冒犯
No offense.
想想二月的码头
So imagine february on the docks.
你戴着哥特龙纤维手套 试着按那些按键
You're wearing gortex gloves, trying to punch numbers on that thing.
你是说那个装着女尸的 集装箱就是这么失踪的?
You're saying that's what happened to the can with the girls in it?
Beadie 亲爱的 我不知道是怎么回事
Beadie, darling, I don't know what happened there.
我只是说 如果你查电脑...
I'm just saying, if you go by the computer...
你会以为里面有什么小猫腻...
It might look like there's some dirt going down...
其实可能只是个电脑的小故障
When it's really just a glitch in the system.
那箱子的海关封条破了
The customs seal was broke on that box.
难道你们没注意到
Shouldn't that get noticed?
你卸的可是有小镇那么大的一艘货船
You're offloading a ship the size of a small town.
你可能会注意到那封条 也可能不
You might notice a broke seal, you might not.
听着 你想再逼问我们 随意
Look, you wanna keep pulling our chain, you can.
但只是一个箱子失踪了
But it ain't like it's just that one box that went missing.
弄丢这些狗娘养的是常有的事
We lose them sons of bitches all the time.
Frank把你们想知道的都告诉你们了吗
Frank give you everything you need?
他说了 谢谢
He did, thanks.
他们在耍我们
They're playing us.
你带着憧憬大老远从Baltimore过来?
You drove all the way from baltimore on a hope and a prayer?
嗯 我的调查陷入死胡同了
Yeah, i'm dead-Ended on this.
我们能跟她们做些交易 以寻求合作吗?
Is there anything we can offer any of them for cooperation?
你可以跟她们中的一个结婚
You could marry one of them,
让她做个美国家庭主妇
Make her an american housewife.
如果不这样 她们从哪来就得回哪去了
Short of that, they're going back the fuck where they came from.
- 你把她们关在哪 - 郡拘留所
- Where do you hold them? - County detention.
我们不会把无证外侨关在普通囚区
We keep the undocumenteds out of gen pop.
你们听说过世通吗
You all heard of worldcom?
好吧 我们试着理解看
All right, let's try this.
你们被警察抄了
You all get jacked by some knockos.
你们身上很干净 只是身负未执行的逮捕令
But you all clean. You all got an outstanding warrant,
就像在座的各位一样 你们怎么办
Like everybody in here. What do you do?
谎报名字
Give another name.
为什么
Why?
因为你的真名会坏事
Because your real name ain't no good.
对 真名不好而且....
All right, it ain't good and....
接着说
Follow through.
好了 现在"死亡之握"很烂
All right, death grip ain't shit?
那就换个名字
Then change up the name.
还有呢
What else?
我想到了 把红盖换成蓝盖 对吗
Yo, i got it, change the caps from red to blue, right?
让人以为我们有了新玩意
Make it look like we got some fresh shit, boom.
- 很好 - 知道我们还能做什么吗
- Yea - You know what else we might could do?
给每栋高楼的货取个自己的名字
Give each tower its own name, right?
让我们之间搞虚假竞争
And then we do, like, some fake competing.
那么 要是毒鬼从一个地方买了烂货
So, a fiend gets some bad shit from one,
他就会到另一个地方
He'd go back to the other.
这孩子有开动脑筋呢
There's a thinking man, right there.
小子 那些难道不是我刚刚说过的吗
See, nigger, ain't that what the fuck i just said?
你跟我叔叔谈过了?
You and my uncle talk?
对
Sure.
情况如何
How'd it go?
没问题
No problem.
三个集装箱
Three boxes.
全是Wilhelmina号上的
All of them on the wilhelmina.
你告诉你叔叔...
And you should tell your uncle...
每个箱子的酬劳是以前的
That it's three times the usual fee
三倍
For each.
我们...
We
查了那些化学品
Checked on those chemicals.
仔细查了查
We looked into that.
你知道 我有些担心
I was worried, you know?
在我送之前 我想知道你们要那些干嘛
Before i deliver, i wanna know what you need it for.
炸弹还是别的什么
A bomb or some shit?
我可不奉陪
I ain't down for that.
你们用那些制毒 是不是
You use that shit to process drugs, don't you?
可卡因
Cocaine.
你们还想要 我会送到Fairfield码头
You still want it, i got it on the fairfield piers.
没问题
No problem.
何时
When?
这周末
End of the week.
Maryska
Maryska.
她英语不错
She's good with english.
她们都死了 我只是想给她们家人带个话
They're dead. All i'm trying to do is get word to the families.
她说什么
What did she say?
她想知道 如果她认识
She wants to know, if she knows a girl,
能留下来吗
Does she get to stay?
你想找间好餐厅吃个饭
You want a good restaurant for dinner,
还是现在就回去
Or are you headed right back?
电脑?
A computer?
查遗失的集装箱
To run a trace on the missing containers
就记录在码头管理部门的数据库里
In the port administration's database.
你们在查什么
You're looking for what?
我们案子的犯罪模式
A pattern for our case.
我们想知道是谁 为什么把那些女孩留在那
We need to know who left those girls on the dock and why.
我们反正要查Sobotka和检查员工会...
We're supposed to be on sobotka and the checkers union anyway...
两案并查也有道理
So folding one investigation into the other makes sense.
对我来说不是
Not to me, it doesn't.
我不会让专案组调查你们的谋杀案
I'm not bringing your open murders anywhere near this detail,
那是个败招
That's a loser for us.
- 警督 - 我们查一些毒品
- Lieutenant! - We bring in a few drug rips,
告诉上面我们迅速 漂亮地 调查了Sobotka和他的工会
And show that we gave sobotka and his union a quick, fair look,
这对Burrell就够了
It's more than enough for burrell.
他再帮个忙 让我离开地下室...
He returns the favor, and i'm out of the basement...
再次回到调查组
And running an investigative unit again.
你让我查我破不了的谋杀案
You dirty me up with murders i can't solve.
这可不成
It doesn't play like that.
凶案组不是个好好查案的地方 警督
Homicide's not the place to sprawl a case, lieutenant.
Rawls
Rawls,
Landsman...
他们只喜欢速战速决 草草收场
They have no patience for anything but a quick shake.
反正 我们有查这案子的资源
We got enough room for it here, anyway.
你们能把这当据点...
You can set up here at the off-Site...
我们可以共享情报
And we can share information.
但谋杀案还是凶杀科的
But the murders stay with homicide.
除非你找到疑犯
Unless, of course,
那又另当别论
You find a suspect.
三艘货轮 四集装箱
Three roiros, four containers.
我把所有的班都排上了
I got all my cards up, including long numbers...
但还是缺人
And we're still short.
- 今天真不错 - 确实
- A good day. - That it is.
今天所有人都上岗
Everybody works today,
连你也有活干了 J级的小鬼
Even you, my little j-Series wonders. Even you.
今天"马面"负责Wilhelmina号吗
Is horse working the wilhelmina today?
我跟那混蛋说了我们不玩了
I told that motherfucker we were done.
我告诉他的
I told him!
他说他跟你谈过了
He said he talked to you.
他说每个箱子三倍的价
He said it's triple-Rate for every can.
三倍?
Triple?
- 打给塔楼上的马面 让他上Wilhelmina号 - 好的
- Call horse in the tower. Tell him he's working the wilhelmina. - All right.
机会只有一次 我别无选择
It's now or never for us, i got no choice.
今天我们有船来了 Frank叔叔
Today we got ships, uncle frank.
今天
Today.
但他妈的是个不祥之兆
But the writing's on the fucking wall.
去他的不祥
Fuck the wall.